completing a project on time requires
finishing piles of tasks timely unless
you manage them productively chaos will
overtake your project management
delaying its completion indefinitely but
Floy boards can turn the tables for you
its functional and reliable task
management features can handle any task
effortlessly so that your project stays
on track let's say you are working on a
marketing project and a new task has
come up open your project board spot the
task option and get it done effortlessly
you can change the title right away if
you need to this is accompanied by
features that help you move tasks to
another board Advance them to different
stages and rearrange them as you like
moving forward you'll come across the
task assignment option choose the icon
and the list of assigned members and
members with access to the board will
appear add a due date set the pro
and fuse customized labels to keep
things sorted now let me present to you
the description box it's fully
customizable describe any task and
highlight key points easily for better
coordination to share any file documents
information or resources attachments can
be your friend in need well it's time to
get your hands on a gamechanging feature
subtasks it helps you break down tasks
into smaller parts besides you can set
deadlines assign team
members convert them into tasks or
simply delete it after completing take
the button and done for instant
communication you can rely on the
comment section anything comes to your
mind related to task completion
modification or guidance share it
freely activities is always there for
you to know what's going on hang tight
I've got a lot more to uncover want to
join the task or move it to another
board stage or position you have full
control if you prefer not to join but
still want to stay informed turn the
watch on and get notified of every task
update and cover enhances task
visibility among others here comes the
template you can create a template out
of any task and use it later next up
custom field whether you prefer a text
field
number field multi select date or
checkbox choose the option that best
fits your needs once the task is
completed archive it and it's gone from
the project board easy right flin board
sets itself apart from other project
management tools with its built-in time
tracking feature estimate task durations
and let ass signes log their time along
with descriptions for smooth completion
of the task soon this will be automated
making your workflow even more seamless
and its integration with fluen CRM
allows you to add contacts directly to
your task need any information about
your clients it's at your
fingertips as I made a template out of
it now I can reuse it as many times as I
need moreover clicking on the three dots
will bring up the features I've used so
far simple and intuitive that's all
about managing t tasks with flu boards
with sorted tasks you're already one
step ahead of managing your project
better like this one you can add and
personalize any task easily and get it
done in time whether you want to say
goodbye to switching platforms or manage
tasks proficiently you can count on
fluent boards act fast and secure your
copy before the deal ends so are you in